

Luis Pedro Bonomi

I am a Fullstack developer with industry experience building websites and web applications. I am specializing in Node React and have 4+ years of professional experience with PHP and JavaScript.



Montevideo, Uruguay http://lpbonomi.com in in





Professional Experience



Fullstack Developer · Gumpo Ltd

Jan 2022 - Present

As a Full-Stack Developer at Gumpo, I was responsible for building and maintaining the different web platforms using Next.js. I was part of a cross-functional team that delivered high-quality solutions for clients.

During my time there, I developed and implemented various features for the platform, including an e-commerce system that provided different hardware solutions for dentists.

Working in an English-speaking environment allowed me to enhance my language skills, making it easier to communicate and collaborate with team members and clients from different cultural backgrounds. Overall, my experience at Gumpo provided me with the opportunity to work with cutting-edge technologies and helped me grow as a developer.



Fullstack Developer • Biller

Jan 2018 - Jul 2021

At biller.uy, I was part of the dev team, contributing to backend and frontend development using Yii2. I migrated logs to Cloudwatch for better management and testing environment from Travis to Github Actions. I implemented complex new bill type using TDD, batch billing for big businesses, and helped onboard new team members.

Education



2017 - 2023

Universidad de la República

Software Engineering



2022 - 2022

Universidad Complutense de Madrid

Exchange Program

Skills

- Web Applications
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Node.js
- Next.js

Languages

- English Professional
- Spanish Native
- French Beginner